[{"answer": "You know, it's interesting and it's very hard as you might imagine, Piers to think any large community including the medical one with one broad brush.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Are they of the belief that this is in the end, going to be a force for good or do they believe as many Republicans would have us believe that this is really deeply troublesome?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well I think it became clear fairly early on the first couple of days that ...", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "UPTA: The President did say that he was angry about this, I mean, do you know when he first knew that there was a problem?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "So not before that though?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "I think that we talked about having testing going forward and if we had an ideal situation and could've built the product in, you know a five-year period of time.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "There was no concern at that point even the White House or at HHS?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "I mean, I asked her three separate ways, you know, I mean, and certainly, I'm not the only asking her this question.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What was your gut feeling when you finish the interview?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "What I talked about is doing the job that I came here to do.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Did you ever talk about resigning to the President?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "I think my job is to get this fully implemented and to get the website working right and that's really what I'm focused on.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "If this persist or even at this point now, would you consider resigning over this?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, it's a huge list but I'm a friend of Kathleen's and I'm a friend whenever she's in trouble.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Occasionally, I have to chop it off, but basically, I believe in sticking by people.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "What is your normal strategy?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I would love to be judged by the two Howards.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "When you look down the line here, what do you feel about these two guys?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Well, what I've learned growing up in our family is that, you know, integrity is everything.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "And I knew then I had a deal because Howard, the Buffett handshake means a lot, right?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Regardless of any piece of paper.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Regardless of any bit of paper?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Yes, I prefer to do business with people I like.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "And do you still prefer to do business with a handshake?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well both my grandfather and my father have been the most amazing role models that anyone could imagine.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "But let me ask you, HWB, what is the single best lesson you have learned from the elder Buffetts in your life, so far would you say?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Well, it's to look at stocks as part of the business rather than little things that blob up and down.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "So we've got plenty of tweets pouring in Jane Fagan Smith (ph) said what's the most important advice you've ever had about investing that you would impart to others?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, I enjoyed them.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Do you have to personally enjoy the stocks that you buy big in?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "So we used a major rock star writers, there was one request, anything Coca-Cola related?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, I don't throw anything away until I got it 20 or 25 years.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "How long have you had that one?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I do it through my assistant.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Do you use e-mail?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I sent it to Jeff Wright at Microsoft and it ended up in court in Minneapolis court.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Who to?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Well, it's not so old.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, I have everything I want, you know, I'm happy.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "You're not into flash things, are you?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Yeah, and I try to feed him candy and pie and all this ....", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "... the rent went down?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "So it didn't work?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I would say it was dumb.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "This deal, I mean it's instinct that the two incentives one worked and one didn't would you regret the weight incentive that you laid down with your son?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think I've ever done that.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Do you have the same criteria?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Well, for one thing, if they combine their credits, we can get one degree and that's", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "You don't seem to face, why?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "$34 billion all of it.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "How much did you pay?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Sure, sure.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Do you ever make big mistakes?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Well, I bought company in the mid '90s called Dexter's Shoe and paid $400 million for it.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "That's -- If you look back, must be the one you think I should never have done that?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Many say the brains really behind the power, would you agree with that Warren?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, I had a roll of windows in my room and, you know, I open the window up, we had this greenhouse so I'd be careful climbing out because I don't want to go through the glass, but I got down and we had our charge account at the local hardware store about five blocks away and I went up there and I convinced the guy to let me charge a has plaque (ph) and buy a screw driver because I don't have any tools and I get everything I needed and I called back up in and I lock her out.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "But not you Howard, what did you do?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I think as it is, she probably got a kick out of it.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "How did you mother react?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I slowly grew up and I wouldn't otherwise at that.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "How did you change?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Sure, sure.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Just to override, anything else you would write?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Well, I want them to be good citizens, good parents that the -- what the world would be better off because they were here.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Well, what are the key values that you would like to see other people recognize in your children, your grandchildren, your family or extended family?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not sure I can give you a great one.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "What is your definition of that?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I'm not sure what are the time lock is.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "He said it's thread bare and dust and has cobwebs, right Howard?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, the \"Forty Chances\" kind of sort of actually my career farming.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Howard tell me about this book \"Forty Chances\", why the title?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, one of the biggest things I've learned is -- I mean there's a lot of great organizations out there.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Well, he's operating on a premise as are my other two children and with the Gates Foundation too that all lives have equal value.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "What do you make of what he's achieved?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I am very proud of him.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "You're proud of him?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, that ranges at a corporate.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Can you do any better on salary?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "ARREN BUFFETT: I wouldn't say that, but nice thing about being mildly famous is that the worst you are the better people like it.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "More on Buffett negotiating with the gang on NBC is the office that led him the attention to details, I'm with his family, one of the most influential in the world back now with the three generations of Buffets, Warren, Howard G, and Howard W. Do you enjoy being actor there, Warren, well you're quite good?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Well, I must take a look.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "If I was to ask you that now what might the answers be?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "I got this wallet for -- here's my.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Is this Edward (inaudible) on television before?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Probably about 20 years maybe.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "How long have you had it first?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Here's my American express card from 1964.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "And what do you had in it?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Yes, well it goes with my cellphone.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "That's the one you have the whole time?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Well, I've variety of card, but there's a picture of the family.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What other cards do you have?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "More than usual that ...", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "And how much cash?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "The resiliency of people.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Let me ask you Howard of all the places you've been, of all the issues you've dealt with, what has been the most powerful to you personally?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Terrific, terrific.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "What is the future for America incorporated, do you think?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Well, you can multiply the bag of purchase but it's all going to -- it's all going to (inaudible).", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Do you know how much your worth?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Very few people.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Pretty illustrious club, right?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "No, I've never met Frank Sinatra.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Have you ever met Frank Sinatra before he died?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "And I'm a fan.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "You're a fan?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Yes, and you just have ...", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "And you were fan of ukulele?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "We had a lot fun.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "I've been inundating with tweets, many of them are saying these Buffett boys are a lot of fun are they?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I've enjoyed it a lot.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "How do you enjoy the last hour?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "A teacher, teacher.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "The time with my dad, that moment, any moment.", "docId": "131022pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Which moment would you choose?", "qSentId": 611}]